I've made up my mind.
I'm retiring.
I'm tired of this.
Thank you sincerely...
for your love and support.
Thank you.
[One year ago]
Today was a handful.
But you guys make it worth it.
[Hello, Khun, I'm a fan of girls...]
[F**k with me]
[I need money]
[Hot body]
[My hair]
[My nail]
[Khun, I miss you and love you]
[Khun]
[Couple toothbrush]
[Don't worry about others
because we only have each other]
Why are you filming me? Stop it!
Where's the library?
I'm not sure.
Sorry.
You're a foreigner?
[Korea]
[Khun]
Ugh, so it is true.
He's really popular.
What do I do?
- It's okay.
- No, no!
I'm not comfortable with this.
I'll do anything.
Cheers.
So.
This was your plan from the start?
Plan?
- What plan?
- Plan to get...
close to me.
Jae Min.
Oh.
You're here.
I didn't think you'd come.
I gave you my word.
Well, you asked me...
if this was all a scheme.
Plan.
Did you say that because you're a celebrity?
That I deliberately approached you to use you?
Is that what you meant?
I don't understand...
what you mean.
Did you think...
that I was using you?
A lot of people do that.
Those people...
did they act as I do?
Do you want me to stop bothering you?
Would you trust me then?
Don't talk... and don't meet you.
Is this my fault?
So I've got to say sorry?
No, I never said that.
Then why are you talking like that?
- What did I do?
- If you didn't know,
you could've just said so!
That you didn't know I was an idol!
That you're Korean,
so that it wasn't your intention!
That would've been enough.
You could've just been honest!
I can't understand you.
Why are you acting like I'm being sensitive?
I was in pain in Thailand!
That's why I came all the way here.
I gave you a piece of my heart.
But now that things have come to this,
I have the right to be confused!
- Hey, why do you keep speaking in Thai?
- Because I'm Thai!
What do you...
want me to do now?
How should I know?
Don't you want to talk?
I said I can't understand you!
Let's just be...
classmates.
Classmates?
I thought maybe I could be normal...
with you.
I thought you might be different.
But since I found out
that you were a trainee...
I can't.
I don't think I can do this.
You might also...
use me for your own good.
Okay.
I get it.
Let's do that.
Just be classmates.
Good night.
Hey, want to go take a vocal lesson after this?
I need to give something to the manager.
You go ahead.
I've been waiting for you.
- Really?
- Let's go.
Why is he following him around like some puppy?
One and two.
Three and four.
Five and six.
Seven, eight.
Good.
This will be the evaluation.
I'll give you an hour to practice.
Give it your all, got it?
- Yes.
Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Get to it.
Hey, what did I tell you?
Stop splitting up. Work together, okay?
You should practice as a harmonious team.
Shall we?
We're a family now, like the mentor said.
But I want to practice with you.
Let's be honest.
A test is better when the participants
already have chemistry together.
Yoon Soo An. Let's team up.
It'd be better to mix things up.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Five, six, seven, eight!
Okay!
The line of movement is great.
It's great, but why are you so stiff?
Did you guys have a fight?
You need to scooch up, get closer.
You guys make it look awkward.
I'm going to check on you guys again.
In the meantime, practice some more.
Good luck on the debut team evaluation.
That's it.
- Thank you, sir.
They're settling your
debut team this week, right?
Yeah. How about you?
Not yet.
I guess we girls have to wait until next year.
Yet you're working so hard already.
As I should!
Maybe I should quit.
Get yourself together, you!
The timing is perfect, and you're talented!
What's your problem?
I just don't feel like this is for me.
- You mean, Hyun Jae?
- No.
Wait, where did that come from?
It's nothing.
I guess things didn't go to plan.
Do you know something?
Oh, it's just that he wanted to see you.
Hey, Hyun Jae has been looking for you.
As a Next Stage Mallangs fan,
I can't just let this slide.
You should keep up with stuff like this.
[They're merging with PNJS?
Wish the best for Soo An!]
[It's been way too long! Time for the stage!]
You can quit if you'd like to,
but people are waiting for you,
more than you'd think.
I don't know how much weight you hold up to it.
But I'd be happy to have fans like this.
Sounds like a dream to me.
I still have a long way to go,
but I'm going to work hard...
for the people that I cherish.
I'm asking you on behalf of all your fans,
Yoon Soo An.
Is everybody working on their assignments?
It's due next week,
so make time for each other.
Talk and learn more about them,
and I expect your notes by then.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Do you have to leave right now?
Not really, no.
We still have a group project to do.
Oh.
Why did you sit in the back?
Just because.
We are in the same group.
Yeah, I guess.
Let's just keep working.
Why aren't you writing?
You know who I am now.
You already know me.
I don't want you to
get the wrong idea about me.
- Wrong idea?
- Misunder...
Never mind.
Khun.
We don't have to meet up
if you're uncomfortable.
I can drop this class.
I don't care about debuting, too.
Don't worry.
Did I ever say something like that?
I said,
we will be classmates.
And?
You think what you're doing right now
is called a classmate?
Not everyone will be promised a debut.
All of you might make it,
or you might not.
We would've debuted ages ago,
if not for what happened with Unicorn!
Go back to Unicorn, then!
So, where are you off to?
Don't talk to me like that.
Still coddling that Thai guy,
and for what, huh?
Or...
is he Shin Jae Min's type?
Do you want it, too?
A scandal?
Don't be ridiculous.